PATRICIA CIBOROWSKI

2716 NE Flanders Portland, OR 97232 (281) 748-8847

HYPERLINK "mailto:ppatriciastudent@aol.com" ppatriciastudent@aol.com

OBJECTIVE

To obtain a profession at a progressive company where I can use my skills to reach the goals set by the organization.

SUMMARY

A professional with ten years of experience in sales, marketing and communication, where she exceeded quotas set by the company. Adept at organizing and problem solving; as well as having the capability to deal with authority and assert authority. Her ability to communicate as a trilingual with 185 hours of sales training has allowed her to overcome barriers. Her goal is to work towards higher standards for businesses that operate through sales, marketing and communications. Her goal, through employment with your company, is to both capacitate and bring revenues to groups that practice sales and marketing through individual and corporate communications.

EDUCATION

University of Houston,

January 2006 – December 2008

Houston, TX

BA in Corporate Communication, completed in December of 2008

Certification in Entrepreneurship: Trained in the entrepreneurship program Enrolled in the Program for Excellence in Selling, nation's #1 sales program

Graduated with honors: Cumm Laude (GPA 3.49)

INTERNSHIP

New Energy Power Solutions

Admitted into internship program through the School of Communications

Conducted presentations for customers

Visited with potential clientele of both residential and commercial properties

Managed account status

Media productions

Houston Community College,

January 2003 – December 2005

Houston, TX

Associates Degree in Art

Transfer student to the University of Houston

EXPERIENCE

CWA Dental Lab

Houston, TX

Dental Technician Assistant and Sales

July 1994 – July 1998 / June 2004 - May 2011

Engineered model work of mouth structure through use of high tech mechanics

Pick ups and deliveries at offices of dentistry

Invoices/ Bill summaries

Phone communication services/ Skills

Service/Product Sales: Established 10 key accounts

CWA Contractor

Houston, TX

Assistant Manager

January 2009 - May 2011

Invoices/ Bill summaries

Phone communication services/ Skills

Service/Product Sales

Designed/Created/Posted advertisements for machinery and service sales

Managed inventory for all projects

T-Mobile

Houston, TX

Professional Retail Sales Associate

September 2009 – December 2009

Built service relationships with clients on a daily basis

Honed professional sales and technology techniques

Product/Service Sales

Intensive product/Service training

Phone communication services/Skills

Managed customer account status through Streamline

Abash

Houston, TX

Secretary Sales and Assistant

July 1998 - March 2004

Appointment/ Reservation book keeper

Invoices/ Bill summaries

Phone communication services/ Skills

Service/Product Sales: 350 plus sales per year

SKILLS

Ability to communicate in English, Spanish, and Polish

Graduated with honors from Elsik High School

Attended volunteer work At Second Blessing from 2002 – 2004

Adept in utilizing Microsoft Word, Excel, Powerpoint and additional computer programs.

CERTIFICATIONS AND LICENSES

Certification in Sales

Certification in Entrepreneurship

License in Life and Health Insurance

License in Property and Casualty